翻译：CharlesChouBlues
时间轴:@经典电影的那点事，匹配蓝光版本
Our father,who art in heaven,
我们在天上的父
hallowed be thy name.
愿人都尊你的名为圣
Thy kingdom come,
愿你的国降临
thy will be done on earth as it is in heaven.
愿你的旨意行在地上 如同行在天上
Give us this day our daily bread,
赐给我们日用的饮食
and forgive us our trespasses,
赦免我们的罪
as we forgive those who trespass against us.
如同我们免了人的债
Lead us not into temptation,
不教我们遇见试探
but deliver us from evil.
救我们脱离凶恶
For the kingdom,the power,and the glory are yours,
因为国度 权柄 荣耀 全都属于你
now and forever.
直到永远
Amen.
阿门
Looking at mostly cloudy skies
大部地区都将继续维持多云天气
and with lows in the upper 20s.
最低气温华氏20度
There will likely be some refreeze on some of the roads.
部分路面可能会再次结冰
So,slick spots are possible tonight in isolated lo...
因此今晚个别偏远地区将出现路面打滑的情况
You know the most important thing
知道你爷爷教会我的
your granddad ever taught me?
最重要的事情是什么吗?
Be ready.
时刻做好准备
Hurricane,flood,whatever it ends up being.
飓风 洪水 无论遇到什么灾难
No more food gets delivered to the grocery store,
哪怕食品店断货
gas stations dry up.
储油池见底
People just turn on each other,and,uh...
人们彼此拔刀相向 或者...
All of a sudden,
其它突发情况
all that stands between you and being dead is you.
你都必须明白 唯有自救 才能生存
I'm proud of you,son.
我为你感到骄傲 儿子
It was a nice shot.
那一枪打得漂亮
Put your hand in the hand of the man who stilled the water
牵着他为你遮风挡雨的手
put your hand in the hand of the man who calmed the sea
牵着他让波涛止息的手
take a look at yourself
看看如镜水面上映出的你
and you can look at others differently
想想众生在这世上都是唯一
By putting your hand in the hand
你只要牵着他的手
of the man from galilee
这男人来自加利利
every time I look at the holy book,I want to tremble
每当我看见圣经 便不由感激颤抖
and then I read about the part
每当我读到
where a carpenter cleared the temple...
那木工清扫寺庙...
Hey,come on,hon.
快点  宝贝
Wait,wait,wait. I forgot something.
等等 等一下 我忘了东西
Hold on a second,Anna!
等我一下 安娜
Ralph,you have the venison?
拉尔夫 你拿上鹿肉了吗
Yup.
拿了.
I forgot the pie.
我把派给忘了
Are we taking the truck?
我们要坐小卡车去么
We're going up the street,you dope.
我们就到街对面 小傻瓜
Come on.
走吧
Hey,wait for your mother,please.
嘿 等等妈妈.
Give me a ride.
我要骑大马
Here.
来吧
Oh,you're gettin' heavy.
噢 你真是越来越重了
Um,Danny's dad said he'd sell me their old car.
丹尼的爸爸说他要把他的旧车卖给我
I got half of what I need saved from the summer.
今年夏天我已经存够一半钱了
- I thought maybe you'd...- forget it.
- 我在想你能不能.... - 别想了
I can barely get enough carpentry work
现在的木工活太难接
to keep up with the mortgage.
就目前的状况看连还房贷都成问题
Well,why don't you rent out grandpa's old apartment house?
为什么不把爷爷的老房子租出去呢
Like I keep telling your mother,it's an old building,
我不是一直和你妈说那房子太旧了么
and it'll cost a fortune to fix it up.
要修好它也得花一大笔钱
Okay,okay.
来了来了
They're here!
他们来了!
Hello.
你好啊!
Happy Thanksgiving. Happy Thanksgiving.
- 感恩节快乐!  - 感恩节快乐!
Anna,wait until we're invited.
安娜 要等人家邀请你才可以进去,
Oh,for God's sake,Keller.Get the hell in here.
看在上帝的份上 凯勒 快点进来吧
Aah!
啊!
Keller,you got the deer you shot?
凯勒 这鹿是你打来的么
This one's Ralph's.
这头是拉尔夫打的.
Well,you killed it,you take it into the kitchen.
既然是你打的 你就负责把它拿进厨房去
All right. Thank you.
- 好的. - 谢谢
Happy Thanksgiving.
感恩节快乐
- Happy Thanksgiving. - There he is.
- 感恩节快乐. - 他在这儿呢
Thank you. Happy t-day.
谢谢.感恩节快乐
All right.Joy. Joy,three times.
好了 乔伊 乔伊 都跟你说过三次了
Joy,get your dolls off the table.Y'all missing the game.
- 乔伊 把你的娃娃们从桌上拿走 - 你们都错过游戏了
- Anna! Anna! - Hi. How are you?
- 安娜 安娜! - 嗨 你好吗?
Hey. Happy Thanksgiving.
嘿 . 感恩节快乐.
Anna,come here.
安娜 过来这里.
We wait until we're invited.You understand?
我们要先得到别人的邀请才可以进去 懂了吗？
You're in charge of this.
你来弄这个吧.
Us veterinarians make lousy butchers.
我们兽医切起肉来还真不在行
No problem.
没问题
Can I go outside with joy?
我可以和乔伊去外边玩吗?
Uh,convince your brother to go with you,and you can.
你能拉上你哥哥陪你一起去就行.
All right.
好了
And wear a hat,please.
记得戴上帽子
You're just getting over a cold.
你感冒才刚好
Joy,you wear a hat,too.
乔伊 你也一样
Did you feel bad for that deer
你打死那头鹿的时候...
when you shot it?
是不是觉得有点难过？
Do you feel bad for cows when you go into McDonald's?
你去麦当劳的时候也为那些牛感到难过么？
That's... that's what my dad says.
我爸就是那么跟我说的.
And the deer,if they have too many babies,
说到鹿嘛 如果它们生了太多小鹿
then the babies starve anyway.
那些小鹿最后也会饿死的
You gotta keep the population down.
所以你需要控制种群的数量
Right. Your dad say that,too?
也对 这也是你爸和你说的么
Pull harder.
用力拉.
Hey,hey! Get away from that thing!
嘿 嘿! 离那辆车远一点!
Let me see that.
让我来试试.
Come on,let's go.
快点 我们走吧
No.
不.
I said let's go!
我说了 我们走！
Stop. You can't just take somebody's stuff like that.
下来 你不能随便碰别人的东西
No! Let's go!
不能上去 我们走吧!
Come on. Come on,come on,come on.
听话 听话 快下来
Wait. Shh.You hear that?
等等 嘘..你听到了吗?
Somebody's in there.
有人在里面.
All right,I don't feel like getting yelled at.
这下好了 我可不想被车主骂
Let's go. Not on Thanksgiving,okay?
我们走吧 感恩节的时候别惹事 知道了吗
Now the school board's telling me
现在 学校董事会告诉我说
there's no money for new marching-band uniforms.
他们没钱给军乐队买新制服
These kids are wearin' the same uniforms
我们去那里的时候
they had when we went there,and they were old then.
那些孩子们还穿着原来的旧制服
I mean,marchin' right out of 1979.
和1979年那会一模一样
Why isn't he speaking to me?
为什么它不跟我说话
He doesn't speak.
它不会说话
Cutie pie.
可爱吧
Mm-hmm.
嗯嗯.
Oh,my gosh!
喔 天哪!
He's fast,too.
它跑得可快了
He's so quick.
Is that a slide?
太快了 那是个滑梯吗?
Thank you,all. Thank you,all. Got a surprise.
谢谢大家 我要给你们个惊喜.
And I am taking requests.
我可以给你们来一个『听众点播』
Yes! No.
- 好! - 别
You gotta listen out for it,'cause this is not easy.
你们都得好好听听 这可不是件容易事
Mom. Mommy,can I take joy to our house?
妈妈 我可以带乔伊去我们家吗
Why?
为什么呀
My red whistle.She's gonna help me look for it.
她要去帮我找我的红口哨.
Oh,my sweetheart,I think that red whistle is long gone.
噢 宝贝 那个口哨早就不见了呀
What whistle?
什么口哨
The emergency whistle daddy gave me.
是我爸爸给我的求救口哨
I lost it...
被我弄丢了...
133 days ago.
...大约133天以前.
Well,if you want to find a whistle,
好吧 如果你想找到它
you have to whistle for it.
得也得先吹几声口哨
So we'll do "jingle bells" to find it.
所以 我们先来表演一首『铃儿响叮当』吧 好不好
Jingle bells,Batman smells,Robin laid an egg
叮叮当 蝙蝠侠香 罗宾下蛋黄
the Batmobile lost its wheels,and joker got away... hey!
蝙蝠车子轮胎掉 小丑逃跑了 嘿！
Yay! Okay! Okay! You can go,all right?
很棒 好了 好了! 你们可以走咯
Just make sure Eliza and Ralph go with you,please.
不过要让伊莱札和拉尔夫陪你们一起去.
- No looking in the basement. - I won't.
- 别去地下室. - 我不会的.
Y'all eardrums are just startin' to grow.
你们要小心你们的鼓膜
I don't want to damage them yet.
我可不想把它们震坏了.
But I am taking requests from you,Keller.
你可以点播一首 凯勒
From me?
我?
Your day,your request.
这是你的日子 所以你先来
Oh. Uh,the piano.
噢 那就钢琴吧
No.
不.
No,no,no. So all set?
不不不不..... 你们都准备好了吗?
Wait,listen,he used to love...
等一下 听我说 他以前特喜欢...
he used to dresslike Springsteen.
他整天打扮得跟斯普林斯汀一样
- Really? - I still love Springsteen.
- 真的吗?   - 我现在还很喜欢斯普林斯汀啊
"The River," "Jersey Girl."
『河流』 『泽西女孩』
Well,I ain't white,and I like him too much
这个嘛 我不是白人 但是我爱死他了
And I'm too drunk to cover the Boss.
不过我现在喝得太多了 没法吹Boss的曲子
（注：Boss是乐迷给Bruce Springsteen起的绰号）
Thank you.
谢谢你
Honey? What else?
亲爱的 还有什么?
Nothing comes to mind. Nothing.
别问我 我脑袋里一片空白
Oh,I know. What?
- 噢 我想起来了 - 什么?
He actually loves "the star-spangled banner."
他还喜欢『星条旗永不落』
I know. Sings it in the shower.
洗澡的时候都会唱
I do not.
没这回事
- Yes,you do! - I got you.
- 怎么没有了！ - 我懂了
Where are your sisters?
妹妹们上哪去了
I can't find them.
我找不到她们了
You,uh,you go to the house with them?
你没有跟她们一起回家?？
No. What are you talking about?
没有啊 什么一起回家？
Earlier? No.
- 早些时候没有? - 没有.
What? They were supposed to come down earlier and get you.
什么？她们之前不是说要下来找你们吗？
They didn't come get you?
她们没来找你？
No. We haven't seen them since we ate.
没有 吃过晚饭后就没再见过她们
It's all right. All right.
没事 先别急
They're probably at our house.
她们可能还在我们家。
Anna? Joy?
安娜? 乔伊?
Anna?
安娜?
Girls?
孩子们?
Girls?!
Who put these dishes in here?
是谁把那些盘子扔到这里的?
Get outta here.They weren't outside.
- 出去吧 - 她们没在外边
It's starting to rain.
外边开始下雨了.
Did you check over by Maria's swing?
你有没有去玛丽娅家的秋千那里看过?
Yeah.
看过了
Well,they're gettin' whupped when they get here.
等她们回来可得好好教训教训
Sorry,Grace.I whup kids.
抱歉 格蕾丝 我得教训下她了
So they weren't there either?
她们也不在那边?
They must be at home.
她们肯定在家
Are they here?
她们在这里吗
No. They're not here.They weren't there?
- 不在 - 她们也没在那边?
No,they're not at our house.
没有 她们不在我们家.
No,they're not there.
她们没在那边.
I checked the entire house.They're not here.
我把整个房子都找遍了 都没见着她们
The... the...the RV.
那辆...那辆小房车
What RV?
什么小房车?
Dad,there was this RV,and they were playing on it.
爸 之前那里停了一辆房车 她们爬上去玩来着
We thought there was someone inside.
我们觉得车里好像有人
Where? Where was it? Show me.
哪里？车在哪里？指给我看
You wait here.
你在这里等着
I'm gonna gonna over the house again.
我在房子里再找找看.
Relax. Relax.
别急 别急
Go that way. I'll meet you on the other side.
你去那边 我们分开走 到那边会合
Anna?!
安娜?
Joy!
乔伊!
Roger,you seen my daughter walk by here?
罗杰 有没有看到我女儿经过这边？
No. Is there a problem?
没看到 出什么事了?
Anna?
安娜?
Here!
就是这里!
Dad,it was parked right here.
爸 那辆车当时就停在这里.
Anna? Anna?
安娜? 安娜?
Hello,hello!
有人吗? 有人吗?
Did you see 'em? No!
- 你看到她们了吗? - 没有
Hello!
有人吗！
I couldn't find 'em!
我找不到她们!
Were you messing around in this house? - No.
- 你们是不是在这捣乱来着  - 没有.
I told you not to come here. We weren't.
- 跟你说过不要来这里 - 又不是我们要来的
They were just on the RV,and we got them off of it.
当时她们在那辆房车上玩 我们过来只是要把她们抱下来
Tell me everything you remember about that rv.
好好想想那辆房车长什么样子
Everything. A-a ladder on the back.
- 仔细想想 - 车后有个梯子
Police,police.
报警 报警
Happy Thanksgiving.
感恩节快乐.
Thanks.
谢谢.
Hey,you have any of those,um,fortune-cookie things?
嘿 你们这里有没有卖...那种幸运饼干？
My boss told me cops don't like fortune cookies.
我老板说警察不喜欢幸运饼干
What year were you born?
你是属什么的?
Are you a dragon or a snake or a horse?
龙？或者蛇？还是马？
I'm a monkey.
我属猴
Oh,you're a monkey.
噢,你是属猴子的.
You're very intelligent.
你非常聪明.
You have an ability to influence people.
拥有某种可以影响他人的能力
Think maybe you could influence your boss
也许你可以试着去影响下你的老板...
to lower the check a little bit?
少收我一点钱
No. I cannot.
这可不行
My boss is a rooster.
我老板是属鸡的
Silly,selfish,and eccentric.
属鸡的人：愚蠢 自私 古怪
That's...
这是有点...
All units,all units,
各小队请注意 各小队请注意
an RV was reported matching the description.
发现符合描述的小型房车一辆
The vehicle is parked at a rest stop off of route 46,
该车辆目前正停靠46号公路外的一个休息站
northbound,past exit 17.
位于第17出口北外侧
Any available units?
是否有巡逻车辆在目标区域附近？
This is 12-12 responding.
警员12-12 响应
10-80 responding.
警员10-80 响应
This is 13-40.I'm five minutes out.
这里是警员13-40 距目标5分钟路程.
I'll meet the responding units.
我现在过去与小队汇合
12-12 standing by.
12-12 收到待命
10-80 standing by.
10-80 收到待命
13-40. I'm on scene.
13-40 到达现场
Be advised,we're moving in.
小队注意 准备包抄
Whoa! Hey,don't move! Hey!
喂 别跑！
Whoa,whoa,watch out!
小心!
Hey,don't shoot!
别开枪!
Don't shoot!
All right,Sloan,take the right!
好了 斯隆 你去右边
Clear!
安全!
Wait,wait,wait,wait,wait! I got this.
好 等等 等一下 让我来
Gimme that.
把那个给我.
Hey.
嘿.
Hey. I see you in there.
我看到你了.
Show me both your hands right now.
把两只手举起来
Hey,I see you in there!
我看到你了
Show me your hands!
把手举起来！
Both hands right now!
两只手！快点!
That's it.Slow. Slow. Slow!
对 就这样 慢一点！慢一点！
Slow. Slowly. Both hands.
慢一点 两只手.
Both fuckin' hands!
我他妈说了两只手!
Walk! Walk!
走 快走!
Hey!
嘿!
Walk!
快走!!
Get up! Get up!
站起来!起来！
Get up!
起来!
Show me those girls!
孩子们呢!
Show me where you put those girls,huh?
你把那些女孩藏在什么地方?
Where are those girls?
女孩们在哪?
Where are those girls?!
Hey,give me the flashlight.Sir.
警官 把手电筒给我
Show me where those girls...they in the woods?
孩子们在哪里？在树林里吗？
You put them in the woods?
你把她们带进树林了？
Where did you put those girls?
你把那些女孩藏在什么地方了？
You hear me?!
你听见我说话了么
What the fuck is this guy on?
这家伙他妈的怎么回事
He's high on something.
他可能是嗑药了
Put this fucking guy in the car.
把他给我弄到车里去.
Get him in the car. Put him in the fucking car!
- 把他弄上车去 - 快把他弄上车!
Walk! Let's go.
- 快走! - 走吧
Hey,call PSP,tell 'em to send their scent dogs.
给局里打个电话 把警犬带过来
And seal off the whole area.
封锁整个区域
The entrance,all of it.
包括这条公路所有的出入口
Right.
收到
You,come with me.
你 跟我来
No,they weren't playing on your RV?
她们没有在你的房车上玩？
No.
没有.
Okay,take a look at 'em again.
好 再看看她们的照片
Don't recognize these girls?
你不认得这两个女孩 ?
I didn't see them.May I sit down?
我从没见过她们,我可以坐下吗?
What do you do in the RV? Answer my question.
你在车里做什么? 回答我的问题.
Sleep there.
我在那里睡觉
You sleep in there?
你在车里睡觉?
You were sleeping out there?
你说你在睡觉？
In the day?
白天睡觉？
Why was the RV parked outside the house?
为什么你的车会停在那座房子外面
Hmm.
嗯?
I went for a drive?
我去那边兜风
You went for a drive? You weren't driving.
你去兜风?你不是把车子停在那里了吗？
I know for a fact those girls were playing outside your rv.
我知道就是那两个女孩在你的房车外头玩
You weren't driving.It was parked.
你没有在开车 当时车是停着的
Was it a special day?
是什么特殊的日子么？
Were you planning on taking two little girls?
你是不是早就计划好了要带走那两个小女孩
No.
没有.
Have you done that before?
你之前是不是也干过这样的事
No.
没有.
- Did you ask them to come inside? - No.
- 你有没有叫她们上车? - 没有.
You ask them to come inside the RV and then you take them away?
是不是你叫她们上车玩 然后就把她们带走了？
No.
没有
Did you put those girls somewhere?
你是不是把那两个小女孩藏起来了?
May I sit down? Come on.
- 我可以坐下吗? - 快说
- Did you put those girls somewhere? - Please don't touch me.
- 你是不是把那两个小女孩藏起来了 - 不要碰我.
I know you put those girls somewhere.
我知道你把那两个小女孩藏在某个地方了.
You hide 'em? No.
- 你把她们藏起来了? - 没有
How did you hide 'em? Do you tie 'em up?
你把她们藏在哪里? 你是不是把她们绑起来了？
Do you tie 'em up?
你是不是把她们绑起来了?
Huh? Hey. Hey. Hey.
嘿 嘿 嘿.
Look,I know you're a good guy,all right?
听着 我知道你是个好人 好么？
I know you're a decent guy.
我知道你是个老实人.
I'm not tryin' to tell you you're doing anything bad.
我的意思不是说你干了什么坏事.
I'm just tryin' to get the right answers out of you,okay?
我只是想要听你说实话 知道了么?
The real ones. That's all I want.
说实话就行. 只要实话.
Where do you usually park your rv,Alex?
你平时把房车停在哪 亚历克斯？
My aunt's house. Your aunt's house?
- 在我姑妈家. - 你姑妈家?
She lets me park it in the backyard.
她让我把车子停在她的后院里.
The grass don't grow back there anyway.
反正后面也不会再长草了
It was my husband's.
那是我丈夫的车.
For sale,if you want it.
我打算卖了 你要吗？
No,thanks.
不 谢谢.
Well,would you tell me
噢 那能不能请你告诉我
what you're doin' on my property then?
你在我家院子里做什么
I'm just glad to know where he is.
我总算知道他跑哪去了
He's always home before dark,and...
他平时总在天黑前就回到家了 而且...
I just don't understand.
我不明白
That boy has never been in trouble,
那孩子以前从来没惹过麻烦
not a day in his life.
一次都没有
Uh,in the summertime,
嗯,夏天的时候,
he sleeps out in the camper some,but...
他会睡在外面的露营车里 不过...
This time of year,he sleeps in here on the sofa bed.
每年这个时候 他会回沙发上睡的
That's my husband.
那是我丈夫.
We had a fight,jeez,five years ago.
我们五年前大吵了一架 啧啧
Walked out,didn't come back.
他一气之下走了 再也没回来过.
Alex loved him like a father.
亚历克斯很爱他 把他看作亲生父亲
Where are Alex's real parents?
亚历克斯的亲生父母呢？
My husband's brother and his girlfriend,
他是我小叔子的儿子
they died in a car accident when Alex was about 6.
亚历克斯六岁的时候 他和妻子出车祸死了
Sorry to hear that.
我很遗憾
He doesn't have much.
他也没什么东西
What have you got?
找到什么了?
Well,this thing's clean.
里头一干二净
I mean,it's filthy as shit,but we didn't find anything.
我是说 虽然这车脏得像坨屎 不过我们什么线索都没找到.
We didn't find any,uh,wool fibers,anything like that?
什么都没发现？羊毛纤维之类的也没有？
The girls could be wearing some wool gloves or wool hat.
那两个女孩好像戴着羊毛手套或者帽子
No cotton fibers?
也没有发现棉纤?
Well,if he was just usin' this thing to transport 'em,
这个嘛 如果他只是用这车载了她们一程
I might buy that.
没线索也不奇怪.
But if there had been a struggle,
但如果她们在车上挣扎过
I would have found something.
那我肯定会发现痕迹的
I'd start lookin' in the woods by the rest stop.
我会去休息站那的树林里再找找
Yeah.
好吧
Half the uniformed cops in the state
半个州的警力
are doin' that right now.
现在都给调去找人了
When you're done with this thing,
等你检查完这车
can you send a crew over to the aunt's house?
可以派人去趟嫌疑人的姑妈家么
Anna!
安娜!
Anna?!
Thanks for comin'. Franklin birch.
辛苦您了 我是富兰克林·伯奇
My wife's in here.
我妻子在屋里.
Honey?
亲爱的?
Her name's Nancy.
她叫南希.
Detective Loki is...honey?
洛奇警探是来...亲爱的?
These photos are better than the ones my husband gave you.
这些照片比我丈夫给你的要好一些.
You can see her eyes more clearly.
你可以更清楚地看到她的眼睛.
So,did we pass?
我们通过了吗?
I'm sorry,what did you say?
不好意思 你刚说什么?
The poly thing.
测谎仪
The lie detector we took this morning.
今早做的测试
Did we pass?
我们通过了吗?
Oh,yeah,yeah. Sorry.
噢 那个啊 是的 抱歉
Yes,we appreciate your cooperation.
感谢你们的配合
It's embarrassing,all the...all this fuss.
实在是太尴尬了 所有的...所有这些破事...
Everyone's gonna think we're crazy
不管她们藏在哪里 等她们玩腻了回来的时候
when those two come out of hiding,wherever they are.
所有的人肯定都会把我们当疯子看
Do you have some reason to believe they ran away?
你觉得她们可能只是离家出走?
No.
不是的
They're happy.
她们很快乐.
They must have run away.
对 她们肯定是离家出走了.
I think they must have run away.
我想她们是离家出走了.
Right?
对吗?
Um,your police captain told me
你们的局长告诉我说
that you've solved every case that you've ever been assigned.
凡是你接手的案子 你都可以查个水落石出
Is that right?
是真的吗?
Sorry.
对不起.
I am so sorry.
我很抱歉.
Do you... do you have children,detective?
警探 你有孩子吗?
I'm gonna find your daughter.
我会找到你女儿的
We believe that they came back here
我们认为她们昨晚离开伯奇家后
after they left you at the birches' yesterday.
回来过这里.
They were looking for Anna's red whistle.
她们在找安娜的红口哨
Right.
是的
I read your statement.
我看过你的笔录
I'm detective Loki.
我是洛奇警探.
I'm heading up the investigation
我负责调查
into your daughter's disappearance.
你女儿的失踪案
Please sit down.
请坐
Uh,uh,m-my son already told you
我儿子已经告诉过你...
that the guy was inside the RV just watchin' 'em,right?
那辆房车里的人在偷窥她们 是不是？
We haven't found any physical evidence inside the RV.
对 不过我们还没有在那辆车里找到任何物证
Or his aunt's house where he lives.
他姑妈家的房子也是一样
Nothing?
什么都没有？
Alex Jones unfortunately has the I.Q. Of a 10-year-old.
亚历克斯·琼斯的智商仅相当于一个10岁儿童
There is no way that someone with the I.Q. Of a 10-year-old
一个只有10岁智商的人
could abduct two girls in broad daylight and then...
要在大白天绑架两个女孩 然后又让她们凭空消失
Somehow make them disappear.
那几乎是不可能的
Uh,well,how can he drive an rv?
如果是那样 那他为什么会驾驶房车？
If he can't answer a question...
我是说 如果他连问题都回答不了...
Well,he has a legal Pennsylvania license.
这个嘛 他确实有合法的宾州驾照
And he ran,right? They said he tried to run away.
他试图逃跑对吗? 他们说他当时正准备逃跑.
Why... why... Why would he run?
为什么--为什么他要逃跑？
I've just spent 10 hours questioning this boy. Okay?
我刚花了10个小时审讯那个男孩 知道么
I hear what you're saying.
你说的我都明白
Uh... Did... did you give him a lie detector?
那你会给他测谎吗?
You gave us a lie detector. Did you give him one?
你给我们都测过谎了 那你会给他测谎吗?
Sir,I understand what you're asking me. Yes,we did.
先生 我知道你想问什么 是的 我们测过了.
We gave him a lie detector,and there is no way of...
我们给他测过谎了 结果显示他并没.....
A lie detector doesn't work
如果一个人连问题都无法理解
if you don't understand the questions.
测谎仪能有什么用呢？
Well,maybe he wasn't on his own.
那他可能有帮凶
How could he drive an rv
一个智商只有10岁的人
if he has an I.Q. of a 10-year-old?
要怎么驾驶一辆房车呢？
Hey,we're considering all possibilities.
我们要考虑到所有的可能性
I don't think you are considering all possibilities.
我不觉得你考虑到了所有的可能性
I-I hear what you're saying. Sir... sir...you listen to me.
- 我已经听到你说的话了 - 先生 先生你听我说.
Just shut the fuck up for a fucking second!
你他妈的能不能先闭上嘴听我把话说完！
This is what I'm gonna need you to do for me.
我需要你配合我一下
I need you to calm down.
你先冷静.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
对不起 我很抱歉
Please listen to me for a second.
请你听我把话说完
Mr. Dover,I understand this is an incredibly hard time.
多佛先生 我明白现在对你来说一定很难熬
But I have every uniformed police officer in this state
但是现在整个州的警力都已经出动
looking for Anna.
在寻找安娜.
I don't understand what any of this means.
我不懂那是什么意思
They said he ran.
他们说他试图逃跑.
They said he tried to get away.
他们说他当时试图逃跑.
I don't understand why he would try to run away.
我不明白为什么他要逃跑.
We're considering all possibilities,Mr. Dover.
我们会考虑所有的可能性 多佛先生.
I hear what you're saying.
我已经听到你所说的了
I'm not crossing anybody off my list.
我不会漏掉任何人的.
Just... Let me do my job.
剩下的就交给我们
Hey!
嘿
Detective!
警探先生!
- Oh,shit. - Hey!
- 该死 - 喂!
He stays in custody until my daughter's found,right?
在我女儿被找到之前 他会一直待在拘留所里？
Right?
对吗？
We have a 48-hour hold on him
我们只能依法拘留他48小时
that ends tomorrow unless we bring charges.
除非提出指控 不然他明天就会被释放
Well,charge him with something. Charge him.
那就起诉他,起诉他.
Mr. Dover,I understand what you're...
多佛先生 我理解你的...
detective,detective,two little girls
警探先生 警探先生 两个小女孩的命
have got to be worth whatever little rule
还抵不过那些条条框框么
you've got to break to keep that asshole in custody.
你必须想办法把那混蛋继续关着
Now,I know you can't promise me anything.
我明白你现在也不能跟我保证什么
I understand that.
我能理解.
But I'm asking you to be 100% sure.
我只是想请求你一定要谨慎行事
Thank you.
谢谢
I appreciate it.
感激不尽
So you're positive he's innocent,
所以说 尽管你已经确定他是无辜的
but you want to keep holding him?
但你还想继续把他扣在这儿？
Anna Dover's father was on my ass this morning.
安娜·多佛的父亲烦我一早上了
I-I get it. I understand. But it's not gonna happen.
行了 我明白你的意思 可你知道那是不可能的.
I was asking for one more day. Fuck you.
- 就再多关他一天而已 - 去你的
No,no.
别傻了
You find his daughter,he'll forgive you.
你找到他的女儿 他自然就会原谅你
You don't,he's gonna hate you anyway.
不然他就能恨你一辈子
So what's next?
接下来打算做什么?
I'm knockin' on doors all night.
整个晚上我都得去挨家挨户地敲门调查
Yeah,well,you're comin' up on 24 hours missing,
是啊 人不见都快24小时了
and you have exactly shit.
你连个屁都还没找到
No,I've got nine level-three sex offenders
谁说的 我已经逮住九个三级强奸犯了.
living within a 10-mile radius of Fairmont circle.
都住在费尔蒙特周围方圆10公里以内
So if you don't mind...
所以 如果你不介意...
Then go. Yeah.
- 行了 快走吧 - 嗯
Go.
走吧.
It's right here.
就在这里..
Look,I-I'm staying straight,okay?
听着 我是个直男
Well,hey,look.Look,I know you're...
嘿 听着 我知道你....
you like yourself some German porn,huh?
你喜欢德国产的片子是吧
Look,I was...
听着 我...
Father! Open up! It's the police!
神父 快开门 警察！
Father!
神父!
Father.
神父.
You mind if I take a look around?
你不介意我四处看看吧?
Fuckin'drunk.
老酒鬼
What the fuck?
这他妈的是什么?
Whoa.
哇.
Aye. Fuck.
噢 操！
Oh! Please,God! God!
啊 求求你 啊 天哪
What's the name of your buddy down there,huh?
地下室里的那家伙是谁 啊？
What's the name,huh? I don't know his name.
- 叫什么名字？ - 我不知道
You don't know his name?
你不知道他的名字?
I don't know his name.
我不知道他的名字!
Hey,you know what?
你知道吗 神父...
I spent six years in Huntington Boys' Home,father.
我曾经在亨廷顿男童院待过6年
You know the Huntington Boys' Home,right? Huh?
你知道亨廷顿男童院 对不对?
Hurting a fuck like you'd be a real treat for me.
我最喜欢教训你这样的老混蛋了
Why don't you tell me his fuckin' name?
为什么你他妈不告诉我他的名字?
He didn't tell me his name.
他没有告诉过我他的名字.
He came to me for confession.
我来找我忏悔.
He said he'd killed 16 children.He bragged about it.
他说他杀了16个小孩 用的是一种自豪的语气
I convinced him to come back here.
我说服他回来这里
He said he'd kill more.
因为他说他要杀更多孩子
16 children,huh?
16个小孩 是吗?
Let's go,you fucking chicken-hawk!
跟我走 你这个该死的鸡奸犯.
Hey.
嘿.
They're letting him go.
他们放人了
What? The man.
- 什么? - 那个男人.
The police said they're letting him go today.
那些警察说他们今天放人
O-okay.I'll take care of it.
我知道了 我会处理的.
Dad? Keep searching.
- 爸爸? - 继续找.
Where are you goin'?!
你要去哪里
He wants you to write your whole name.
你要写你的全名
That's good.
这样就对了.
Mm-hmm. Good job.
嗯 很好
Now you give it to the man.
现在把它交给那个人.
All right. Come on.
好了 我们走吧.
I don't want you minding these people out here.
别搭理外面那些人
Don't talk to them. You've got nothing to say to them. Come on.
别跟他们讲话 你没话和他们说 我们走吧
Come on,Alex. You took those kids,didn't you?
说说吧 亚历克斯 是你带走了那些孩子 是不是?
Sir...I just want to talk.
- 先生... - 我只是想要跟他谈谈.
He's a free man,I'm a free man!
他是个自由人 我也是自由人
Hey! Tell me what you did with them!
告诉我你对她们做了什么！
Tell me!
告诉我！
They didn't cry until I left them.
我一走她们就开始哭了
What did you say? What did you say?!
你刚说什么？你刚才说什么？
Whoa,no,no!
噢 不不不不...
Fuckin' get off!
放开我！妈的！
God! Get up!
天哪 快起来!
Get him down! Get him down!
按住他！按住他！
Move back!
后退!
Please,just let us go.
拜托了 让我们走吧
We're fine. Thank you.
我们没事 谢谢.
Now,I know your dad was a guard at Graterford.
我知道你爸爸曾经是格雷特福德监狱的守卫.
And I've got a daughter of my own,
我也有个女儿
so we're gonna pretend this never happened.
所以 我们就假装什么都没发生过.
And as for Alex Jones,
至于亚历克斯·琼斯,
he has orders not to leave the commonwealth.
我们暂时会限制他出境
What?
什么?
Sir,I need you to go home. All right?
先生 请你现在回家去 好么
I need you to go home to your family.
你现在先回家吧,回到你家人身边去.
Why aren't you sending someone out to go arrest this guy?
为什么你们不马上派人去把他抓回来
Tell detective Loki what you just told me,
把你刚才告诉我的那些话讲给洛奇警探听
and he'll definitely look into it.
他会调查清楚的
Go ahead.
说吧.
That asshole you promised me you'd keep in custody,right?
你跟我保证过你不会放走他的 不是么
And you didn't.
但你并没有那么做
And right now when I grabbed him in the parking lot,
就在刚才 我在停车场抓着他的时候
he said right to my fucking face,
他居然当着我的面说...
"they didn't cry until I left them."
『我一走她们就开始哭了』
Right to my fucking face.
当着我的面说的
He... he said that to you in the parking lot just now?
这话是他刚刚在停车场跟你说的?
Right now,yeah. What did I just say?
对 就是刚才 我不是说了吗?
In the parking lot.
就在停车场
Before you grabbed me off him.
就在你们把我拉开之前
Did anyone else hear it besides you?
当时还有其他人听见他说这话么
I don't know. It was quiet.
我不知道 他跟我说话时声音很小
He... he said it to me. He wanted me to know.
他跟我说那些是因为他想让我知道
Are you sure he said that? What?
- 你确定他说了那些话? - 什么?
Are you sure that's what he said?
你确定他说了那些话吗?
Jesus Christ,you think I'm makin' this up?
老天 你以为这都我是瞎编的么
No. Why would I make this up?
- 不是 - 为什么我要编瞎话？
Hey,hey,hey,whoa,whoa. No,think about it.
- 嘿 冷静点  - 不 你自己想想.
Why would I make this up? I'm not saying that to you.
- 为什么我要骗你 - 我没那么说
I'm just asking you a couple questions.
我只是问了你几个问题
I will talk to him.
我会跟他谈的
No,don't talk to him! Mr. Dover...
- 别 你别跟这种人『谈』 - 多佛先生
arrest him!
直接逮捕他!
What did I fuckin' tell you?
我他妈的怎么跟你说的?
What'd I tell you? One more day.
我他妈怎么跟你说的? 就多一天！
You sure you didn't say anything to Mr. Dover
你确定在停车场时
in the parking lot today?
你什么都没跟多佛先生说?
Anything he could have misinterpreted or...?
比如一些让他产生误会的话?
I was right there.
我当时也在那里.
They didn't say anything to each other.
他们彼此什么话都没说
Man just attacked the boy.
那男人上来就打
Nothing like "get away from me" or "help" or...
连『离我远一点』或者『救命』之类
Anything like that?
类似这样的话都没说过?
No.
没有.
Can I speak to Alex alone for a minute?
我可以单独跟亚历克斯讲几句话吗?
It's all right,sweetie.
没事的 宝贝
I'll be right in the next room.
我就在隔壁房间等你
You love your aunt,don't you,Alex?
亚历克斯 你很爱你的姑妈 对吗?
Yes.
是的.
You know if you know something you're not telling us
如果你有什么事瞒着我们
that she could go to jail for a very long time.
那可能就会害她坐很长时间的牢
Do you want that for her?
她为你付出了这么多
After everything she's done for you?
你不希望她进监狱 对不对?
No.
不想
Mr. Dover,this is detective Loki.
多佛先生 我是洛奇警探
Have you arrested him?
你有没有逮捕他?
Yeah,look,I just came from Alex Jones,
听着 我刚刚从亚历克斯·琼斯家出来
and he said he didn't say anything to you
他说他在停车场时
in the parking lot.
什么都没有跟你说过
I pushed him pretty hard,and he didn't budge.
我不停旁敲侧击 可他还是坚持那套说法
So,look,we can't waste any more time on this guy.
所以 你听着  我们不能再在他身上浪费时间了
All right? You're gonna have to trust me.
好吗？你必须要相信我
I'll let you know if I have anything new,all right,
如果我这边有任何新的消息
for the...
我会及时...
Fuckin' A
有病
The zipper on her coat was broken,
我看见她衣服上的拉链坏了
and I told her it didn't matter
可我跟她说没事的
'cause we were just gonna go right down the street.
因为我们只是到街对面去而已
No,no.
不 不.
Why hasn't she come home?
为什么她还没有回家?
It's been three days.
已经三天了.
Why can't you make her come home?
为什么你还没有把她找回来?
I don't understand.
我不明白.
I don't understand. It's been too long.
我真的不明白 已经过去这么长时间了.
Please make her come home.
求你们快把她找回来吧
Please make her...
求你们..
How many of these? How many of these?
这个要吃几片? 几片？
How many of these? I don't know!
- 一次要吃几片? - 我不知道!
It's okay. It's all right.
没事 别怕 没事的
Just take one.
就吃一片吧
Here.
拿着
No.
不要
I just want to sleep.
我只想睡一觉.
I just want to go to sleep.
我只想睡觉
You...
你...
You made me feel so safe.
你总能给我安全感
Oh,God...
噢 天哪...
I'm gonna go out and help the police.
我现在要出去协助那些警察
Just keep an eye on your mother.
你照顾好妈妈.
Your sister needs us to be brave for her.
为了你妹妹 我们要坚强一点
Be brave for her.Be a grown-up for me,okay?
你要像个成年人一样 好吗?
Can you do that?
你能做到吗?
能做到吗?
I know you're scared. Look at me. Come here.
我知道你很害怕  看着我 过来这里
I know you're scared.
我知道你很害怕
It's gonna be okay.
一切都会好起来的
The former is a reason why we should be very patient.
前者是我们应耐心等待的理由
The latter why we should be very penitent
后者则提醒 当我们遭受困苦的时候
when we are afflicted.
理应心生忏悔
He reminds him that trouble and affliction
困苦与磨难
are what we have all reason to expect in this world.
是我们生活在这世界所需经受的必须
Man is brought into trouble,not as man,
但困苦并非总是不请自来
but as sinful man,who was in transgression.
犯下了罪的人 那些僭越的人
Man born in sin and therefore born to trouble.
其人生而有罪 因而必得遭受苦难
Come on.
快走
Come on,Tucker.
走啊 塔克.
Jingle bells,Batman smells
叮叮当 蝙蝠侠香
Robin laid an egg
罗宾下蛋黄
the Batmobile lost its wheels
蝙蝠车子轮胎掉
joker got away,hey
小丑逃跑了 嘿
jingle bells,Batman smells,Robin laid an egg
叮叮当 蝙蝠侠香 罗宾下蛋黄
Jingle bells,Batman smells
叮叮当 蝙蝠侠香
Robin laid an egg
罗宾下蛋黄
the Batmobile... - Alex.
蝙蝠车子... - 亚历克斯
Lost its wheel...
轮胎掉...
That song.
那首歌
Where did you hear those words?
你从哪里听到那些歌词的?
Hmm?
啊?
Did you bring a change of clothes like I told you?
你有没有按我说的带上一套换洗衣服
Yeah.You gonna tell me why?
带了 能告诉我原因吗?
It's better if I just show you.
你看了就明白了
Show me what?
看什么?
Didn't you used to live here?
你以前不是住在这里吗？
Close the door.Lock it.
关上门 锁好.
Oh,my God.What... what did you do?
噢 天哪 你都干了些什么？
Keller,what the hell...?
凯勒 这里面是...?
I heard him singing the same song
我听到他唱歌了
they were singing on Thanksgiving.
就是女孩们在感恩节那天唱的那首歌
Swear to God,Franklin. The same fucking song.
我发誓 富兰克林 就是他妈的那首歌
And I told you what he said in the parking lot.
我已经告诉过你他在停车场对我说过什么
Then we take him to the police...
那我们把他交给警察吧
no,no,no.The police won't do shit.
不 不 警察狗屁都干不了.
He'll just clam up and act crazy like he did last time.
他还是会继续装疯卖傻不肯说话 就像之前那样
Someone has to make him talk.
必须得有个人让他开口
Someone.
必须得有人这么做
Shit,man.This... this ain't right.
可是这么做是不对的
I mean,what if you're wrong?
我是说 万一你错了该怎么办？
I'm not wrong. But what if you are?
- 我没错 - 但是万一...
What if you only heard what you wanted to hear?
万一你只是听见了你心里想的东西呢
What if...
万一...
Man,I want my daughter back as much as you do,
听着 我和你一样想找回自己的女儿
but it ain't right. Franklin! Franklin!
- 但这么做是不对的. - 富兰克林 富兰克林!
We hurt him until he talks,or they're gonna die.
他不开口 我们就打 不然孩子们都会死
This ain't...
可是这是不....
No! No!
不 别再说了
We hurt him until he talks or they're gonna die.
他不开口 我们就打 不然孩子们都会死
That's the choice.
二选一
That's the choice you have to make.
你必须做出选择
I've made my choice.
我已经做出我的选择了
I know what I heard.
我知道我听到了什么
He's not a person anymore.
别把他当人看了
No,he stopped being a person when he took our daughters.
从带走我们孩子的那一刻起他就已经不算是人了
I need your help.
我需要你的帮助.
This is your last chance.I know you're scared.
这是你最后的机会 我知道你很害怕
And I know you wanna go home.
我知道你想回家.
And I don't...I don't want to hurt you.
我不想....不想伤害你.
I don't.
我不想.
I'm gonna take the tape off,
现在我帮你把胶布撕下来
and I want you to tell me where they are.
我要你告诉我孩子们的下落
Hey. Come on.
嘿 过来.
Did you see my glasses?
你看到我的眼镜了吗?
What?
什么?
I can't see.
我看不见了
If you're not gonna talk,Alex,I'm gonna have to hurt you.
如果你不说 亚历克斯 那我就不得不伤害你了
Tell me where they are.
告诉我她们在哪？
Where are they?
她们在哪?
Tell me where they are!
快说 她们在哪!
Yeah,I'm out here at a house on Fairmont circle,
对 我在费尔蒙特这边
the house the rv was parked in front of.
就在那辆房车当时停靠的房子前面
It's only been on the market a couple of months.
几个月前这个房子刚刚转手出售
I'm gonna track the owners down,see if they know anything.
我准备去找找房主 看看他们是不是知道点什么
You got any new info on that corpse
关于之前牧师地下室里的那具尸体
we found in the priest's basement?
你有没有什么新发现？
No DNA,dental,or fingerprint matches.
没有DNA 也没找到任何相匹配的牙科记录或指纹
Nothing.
什么都没有.
Priest is sticking to the story,too.
牧师坚称他之前所说的都是真的
All right.
好吧.
Same person who took him took those girls.
我敢肯定 就是带走他的那个人
I'm sure of it.
带走了那两个女孩
Wearing out the tape,I guess.
录像带有点磨损
I watch it every day after breakfast.
每天早餐后我都会看这段录像
It's the only video I have of him.
这是唯一一卷有他的录像带
It was before your time.
拍的时候你大概还没出生呢
26 years ago,August 19th.
26年前的8月19日
I took a nap in the afternoon,
那天午饭后我小睡了一下
and when I woke up,Barry was gone.
等我醒来的时候 巴瑞就不见了
No one could ever tell me what happened to him.
没有人告诉过我究竟发生了什么事
He was playing in the front yard,
他当时就在前院里玩
just a few feet from where they say that rv was parked.
距离那辆房车停放的地方只有几英尺远
What do you think that means?
你觉得那意味着什么?
I'm more interested in what you think that means.
我更想知道你的看法
I don't think we'll ever know.
我们可能永远不会知道了
It's just like Barry.
她们和巴瑞一样
No one took them.
没有人带走她们
Nothing happened.
就像什么都没发生过
They're just gone.
就那么凭空消失了.
How you doin',father?
你怎么样 神父?
I'm... I'm...gettin' better.
我...我感觉好多了.
So detective Chemelinski tells me
季默林斯基警探告诉我说....
that you have some specifics
你知道一些
about the crime you claim that guy committed.
关于你说的那个罪犯的细节
The abductor.
他是个诱拐犯.
He was...
他...
Waging a war against God.
他要向上帝宣战
Great.That's great.
好吧 好吧.
I thought you said he had something specific.
我以为你的意思是说他知道一些细节的东西
Tell him how he took the kids.
告诉他那男人是怎么把孩子们带走的
He said...
他说...
he took them in daylight.
...那些孩子都是他白天带走的.
Sometimes...
有时候...
More than one child at a time.
一次还不止一个孩子
He said that?
他那么说?
Yeah.
是的.
Did he say he was with anybody?
他有提到过帮凶的事么
He did it alone?
还是说他一个人干的
He...
他...
He said he had a family.
他说他结婚了
That's it?
就这样?
All right.
好吧.
Informative.
毫无帮助
You said they cried when you left them.
你说过你一走她们就哭了
Look at me.
看着我.
You said they cried when you left them!
你说过你走的时候她们在哭!
Now tell me!
现在你告诉我
Where is she? Hmm? Hmm?
她在哪!
Tell me where they are!
告诉我她们在哪 !
Just tell me.Just tell me and I'll stop.
快点说 只要你告诉我我就停手
I'll stop as soon as you tell me.
你告诉我 我马上停手
Just...
只要...
Just tell me where they are.
只要你告诉我她们在哪 .
Why won't you tell me?
你为什么不说话?
Huh?
啊?
Why won't you just fuckin' tell us?
为什么你他妈的就是不告诉我?
He knows.
他知道的
他一定知道.
I can see it in his eyes.He fucking knows.
从他眼睛里看得出来 他肯定他妈的知道
I know you know!
我知道你知道!
Why aren't you fucking telling me?!
为什么你他妈的就是不告诉我!
Why?!
为什么?
Fine.
好
Get him up.Get him up. Get up.
把他弄起来 弄起来
Get up. Get up.Get up!
起来. 起来！
You gonna make me use this?
你打算逼我用这个?
You gonna tell us?
你说不说?
If you don't,I'm gonna use this.
如果你不说我就要用这个了
Fine.
好
You're doing this to yourself.
这是你自找的.
Just tell us.Tell me.
快说 告诉我！
Tell me!
告诉我!
Tell me! Tell me!
告诉我!告诉我!告诉我!
Where's my daughter?!
我女儿在哪里！
Where's... My...Daughter?!
我女儿 ！在！哪里！
Four days have passed
从安娜·多佛和乔伊·伯奇的父母
since Anna Dover and Joy Birch
最后一次看见她们
were last seen by their families.
到现在已经过去四天了
The two girls,aged 6 and 7,
这两个小女孩 分别只有6岁和7岁
are believed to have been playing on this street
警方认为女孩们失踪前
when they disappeared without a trace.
正在街上玩耍
As you can see,despite the cold,
正如你所看到的 尽管今晚天气很冷
a lot of people have turned out tonight to show their support.
但依然有许许多多的人来到街上 为两位女孩祈祷
Police are asking that anyone
警方表示 如果任何人
with any information on the girls' whereabouts...
知道有关两位女孩下落的信息....
Where have you been?
你去哪了?
I was searching for her in the woods.
我一直在树林里找她.
I'm okay. I'm okay.
我没事 我没事.
Franklin.
富兰克林
Franklin,what is it?
富兰克林 你怎么了?
I just need a minute.
我很快就好
What the fuck?
搞什么鬼
Hey! Get offa me!
嘿 放开我!
Hey! Hey!
嘿 嘿!
And this is who police are saying
这位就是警方公示的
is a person of interest
与两名女孩的失踪案...
in the investigation of the two missing girls.
有关的嫌疑人
Now,this unidentified man,
该不明身份男子
who was last seen at last night's candlelight vigil,
最后一次出现是在昨晚的烛光守夜现场
fled on foot when the investigating detective
当负责该案件的警探试图盘查他时
attempted to question him.
该男子当即从现场逃脱
Police caution the public not to approach this man,
警方警告公众 请勿接近这名男子
but to call police immediately if they do see him.
如果有人发现该男子 请立即报警
Thanks,John,for that update.
谢谢约翰为我们带来的最新消息
And now for the weather.
现在我们来看看天气状况
We should expect heavy rain into the weekend and...
本周末我们将迎来一场暴雨...
Look,Keller,I mean,just think about it.
听着 凯勒 你好好想想
Why would the police be lookin' for this man
如果警察认为不是这个男人干的
if they didn't think that he did it in the first place?
为什么他们要寻找他.
They did it together.They know each other.
他们肯定是同伙 他们认识彼此.
Listen,I fuckin' told you,all right?
听着 我早他妈的告诉过你了
Jones looked me in the eye and he said,
琼斯看着我的眼睛说……
"they only cried when I left them."
『我一走她们就开始哭了』
He left 'em with someone,and he knows where this guy is.
他把她们留在某个人那里 而且他知道那个人在哪
Holly Jones' dog got hit on southward street.
亚历克斯·琼斯的狗在南大街被车撞了
Apparently Alex Jones took the dog for a walk
很显然亚历克斯·琼斯当时正在遛狗
the night before last...they never came home.
前天晚上 那之后他一直没有回家
And his aunt didn't want to tell us about the dog
他姑妈没老实把那只狗的事告诉我们
when we called her about it this morning.
今天早晨我们打电话给她的时候
She said that she thought
她解释说她觉得...
it would get him into trouble or some shit.
那会让他惹上麻烦
I thought you said you would keep him under surveillance.
我以为你会安排人监视他
Yeah,and I thought you said the guy was innocent.
我以为你说那个男人是无辜的
And I thought the guy from last night you said was our guy.
而且我还以为昨晚那个人才是我们要找的人.
Look,I don't have money in the budget
听着 我没那么多经费
for watching innocent people.
去监视一个无辜的人
You said to me that you'd put him under surveillance.
但你跟我说你会安排人监视他.
What do you want me to say? You gonna keep your word?
- 那你想让我说什么? - 你说话就不能算点数吗?
You could have just given me a call,because I would have
哪怕你就给我打个电话
been there all night. I would have stayed up all night.
那我会待在那里看着他 哪怕熬通宵都没关系
I would know where he was now.
起码我现在就可以知道他去了哪
I need to know where everybody is.
我需要知道每个人待在什么地方
All right,point made. All right? Point made.
行了 我知道了 行了吧
If you can be clear with me,then I'll be clear with you.
你把事整干脆了 我也能和你干脆点
I need to know where everybody is.
我需要知道每个人待在什么地方
If you're gonna do something different,please tell me.
下次如果你要变更计划 请提前告诉我
Tell me about your RV.
告诉我有关房车的事
What do you do in your RV?
你在房车里做什么
It's where I go...
我想一个人呆着的时候
To be alone.
就会去那里
What music do you listen to in your RV when you're alone?
你一个人在车里听些什么
Radio,tape...
广播 还有磁带
The RV was parked over on Fairmont circle?
房车停在费尔蒙特一带？
No.
没有
Is my aunt coming?
我姑妈来了吗?
Have you seen these girls?
你见过这两个女孩吗?
No.
没有
Take a look at 'em.You seen these girls?
再看看照片 你有没有见过她们？
No.
没有.
Did you participate in any way
你有没有以任何形式参与...
in the abduction of those girls?
绑架这两个女孩?
No.
没有
Loki! You got a call.
洛奇 你的电话
All right.
来了
I called as soon as I saw the sketch on TV.
我一在电视上看到嫌犯画像就打来了
He comes in here every week almost
他几乎每周都会来这里
and buys kids' clothes,
买小孩子的衣服
but he's always buying stuff in different sizes.
但是他每次买的都是不同尺寸的衣服
Caught him messing around with the mannequins once.
有次他在人体模特附近搞破坏被抓到了
What did he pay with?
他用什么付款?
Cash.
现金.
All right,you give me a call if you hear anything.
好 如果你有什么消息 及时打电话给我
Okay.
好的
It's been five days.
已经第五天了
Maybe five days since they had a drink of water.
也许她们已经五天没喝水了
This could be the last night that matters.
也许过了今晚就来不及了
Look,I'll call you after Nancy goes to sleep,all right?
听着 南茜睡着后我再打给你 好吗
I promise.
我保证.
Where have you been all this time?
这段时间你都在哪 ?
What the hell were you thinking?
你到底怎么想的?
You tell anyone?
你没有告诉其他人?
Did you?
有没有?
I wanna see him.
我想要见他
Please help me.
请帮帮我.
Could you help me find my little girl?
可以帮我找我的小女儿吗？
Got a picture.
我带了一张照片
See?
看到了吗
This my baby.
这是我的孩子
You see her?
看见了吗?
Her name is joy.
她的名字叫乔伊.
And,um...
还有
This is...
这个是...
A stuffed animal we got her when she was 2
这是她两岁的时候我们买给她的玩具
because she's afraid to sleep by herself.
因为那时她不敢一个人睡觉
Please... Tell me where my little girl is.
求求你...告诉我 我女儿在哪里.
Please tell me where my little girl...
求求你告诉我 我女儿在哪....
I know you're gonna tell me.
我知道你会告诉我的.
I know.
我知道
Help me.
帮帮我.
帮帮我
Franklin,did you close the door to the...
富兰克林,你有没有把门关....
Nancy!
南茜!
What the fuck you doin'?
你他妈的在干什么?
God damn it!Damn!
该死的！见鬼！
Let it go!
把它放下!
You untied him? Huh?
你把他的绳子解开了？啊？
That was close.
差点就让你跑了
What is it? What happened?
怎么了？发生什么事了?
Get Franklin.I need to show you something.
叫上富兰克林 我要给你们看点东西
Did he say anything new?
他有没有说什么?
He will soon.You'll see.
很快就会说的 等着吧
No light gets in.
没有光线.
There's barely enough room to sit down inside.
里面的位置也不够他坐下的
Shower still works,
莲蓬头还能用
but we control it from out here.
但控制阀门在外面
And I rigged the water heater
我把加热器改装过了
so it either comes out scalding or freezing.
出来的水不是滚烫就是冰冷的
And,uh,you talk to him through this.
你可以从这里和他说话
It's to remind us...
这是为了提醒我们...
In case we start feeling sorry for him.
以防我们动恻隐之心
My God.
我的天.
I can't hurt him any more without killing him,
我们不能杀他 所以这是最能折磨他的办法了
so this is the only way.
这也是唯一的方法.
Have you lost your mind,Keller?
你疯了吗？凯勒？
Do you have a better idea,Franklin?
难道你有更好的主意 富兰克林?
Do you?
有吗?
Go ahead.Let him out,if you want.
去吧 放他出来 如果你想的话
I'm not gonna stop you.
我不拦你
If that's what you really want,you go ahead.
如果你真想那么做 就动手吧
You think someone's lookin' out for our girls
你现在在这里可怜他
the way you're lookin' out for him?
谁来可怜我们的孩子
I hope.
希望有这么个人吧
It's been five days now,man.We're runnin' out of time.
已经五天了 我们快没时间了
You don't even know it's him.
你还不能确定就是他干的
Yeah,I do. No,you don't.
- 我能确定 - 不 你不能
I do. I know you. You don't.
- 我很确定. - 我知道你不确定.
Look,I want my baby back...
听着 我现在和你心情一样...
As much as you miss Anna.
我也想让我的安娜快点回来
And despite what you think about me,
我不在乎你是怎么看我的
I would die for my daughter.
可是我可以为了我的女儿去死
But this ain't right.
但我们这么做是不对的..
This has to stop.
我们不能再这样下去了
Well,then,you better get to work.
那你就动手吧
You can start with that wall there.
从那面墙开始拆
Franklin.
富兰克林.
Stop.
别
Franklin...
富兰克林...
Think of joy.
想想乔伊..
I need to get out of this place,Ralph.
我得走了 拉尔夫.
Everything in this house just makes me want to throw up.
这房子里的一切都让我想吐
Your dad's building?
你是说你爸爸的房子?
There is no way I'm staying in that crackhouse.
我没办法待在那个破房子里
It's disgusting.
太恶心了
Yeah,okay.
好吧
We're not gonna help Keller,but we won't stop him,either.
我们不会帮凯勒 但我们也不能阻止他
Let him do what he needs to.
就让他做他想做的事吧
We don't know about it anymore.
我们不要再管那么多了
Eliza?
伊莱扎?
Excuse me.Eliza?
Eliza,open the door!
伊莱扎 开开门.
Eliza?
伊莱扎?
Is she in there?
她在里面吗?
Honey?
亲爱的?
Get out of the way!Get out of the way!
让开! 让开!
Yeah,fuck you both!
你们俩够了!
Next time you plan on leaving me here alone,
下次你们如果打算留我一人在家
maybe you could try at least telling me where you're going!
请至少跟我说清楚你们要去哪里
Ralph?
拉尔夫?
Anna?
安娜?
Mom?
妈?
Anna.Anna was here.
安娜. 安娜刚刚在这里.
Mom,it's freezing in here.
妈 这里怎么这么冷.
Mom! Hey,mom,mom,mom,please sit down.
妈! 嘿 妈 妈 你先坐下
Stop. Calm down.I'm gonna close the window.
别说了 冷静点 我去把窗户关上
And she wasn't here.
她不在这里.
And then I heard a sound from my room,
然后我听到我房间里有动静
and I... I came in and the window was open.
然后...我发现窗户是开着的
And... and it wasn't open before.
并且...窗户之前一直是关着的.
And then... and then Ralph,he... he came in...
然后 拉尔夫进来了
And he looked and... and,um...
他看着我...然后...
And then...
然后..
Then I don't know.
然后...我不知道
Aren't you gonna write this down?
你要不要把这些写下来?
The basement.
地下室.
I didn't check the basement. We need to check the basement.
没有检查地下室 我们得去检查一下地下室
I-I'll show you. I'll show you.
我带你去看看
The kids know they're not allowed down here.
我们不允许孩子们下来这里
They're not supposed to come down here,
他们不应该下来这里
but I-I don't know.
但是 谁知道呢?
My husband likes to be prepared for emergencies.
我丈夫喜欢为紧急状况做准备
Where is your husband,Mrs. Dover?
你丈夫去哪了 多佛太太
I was gonna ask you.
我也正想问你呢
He's been out searching with the police for Anna.
他一直在外边忙着和警察一起找安娜
Which you should be doing right now.
你现在不也该去找的吗?
Does he always stay out this late?
他总是在外边待到这么晚？
Yes,he stays out this late
对 他总是在很晚才回来
when he's looking for my daughter,
每次他说要出去找我们女儿的时候
since my daughter has been gone... yes!
从我们的女儿不见开始...是的!
Shit.
该死.
Hey,go aro...
嘿 你绕道...
go around.
从边上绕过去.
Fuck.
该死!
Come on,Mr. Dover.
快点吧 多佛先生
Shit.
该死.
Why are you following me?
你为什么跟踪我?
Get in the car.
上车说
Why are you following me?
你为什么要跟踪我?
Where did you go just now?
你刚才去哪了?
I parked at a liquor store.
我去那边的商店里
I have a bottle of liquor.
买了瓶酒
You're the shit-hot detective.Work it out.
你不是神探么 这都看不出来
I actually meant before that.
我是说你进商店前本来准备去哪 ?
You were walking in the opposite direction
你往商店的反方向走了
across the parking lot.
穿过停车场
Towards campello street.
往坎佩罗大街方向
Yeah,well... I haven't had a drink
这个... 我已经有大概9年半
in nine-and-a-half years.
没喝过酒了
I figured if I walked around the parking lot for a while,
我以为在商店开门的时候
by the time they opened,I'd stop wanting it that bad.
在停车场周围走走 就不会那么犯瘾了
And then... then I saw you.
然后 我就看到了你
Sorta helped me make up my mind.
我就忍不住去买了
There's a bag of lye in your basement that's half-empty.
你地下室里的碱液 有一袋用了一半
Your wife thinks you've been helpin' us...
你妻子以为你一直在帮我们...
But we both know that's not true.
但我们都知道那不是真的
I used the lye to bury our dog last year.
去年我埋葬我们家的狗时用掉了一部分碱液
And "helping the cops" sounds better
而且,我之所以说『我在帮警察』是因为这话听起来要比...
than "I've been driving aimlessly in my truck
『我开着车在四处游荡』要好得多是不是？
'cause I don't know what the fuck else to do."
因为我不知道我他妈的还能做点什么
Is that what you were doing last Saturday night?
上周六晚上你也在四处闲晃?
Probably.Am I a suspect?
可能吧 我现在是嫌疑犯吗?
No,I'm only asking
不 我就随便问问
I'm only asking 'cause you assaulted a man who's now missing.
你袭击过的那个男人失踪了
I heard about that.What happened to him?
我听说了 他怎么了?
Thought you had him under surveillance.
我以为你们在监视他呢
I'm gonna assume you're asking me because you have no idea.
我以为你这么问是因为你也不知道
Well,I didn't think it was something I could get away with.
我不认为你会觉得我跟这事没关系
It's not.
不是.
Yeah,well,it couldn't be that he skipped town
他该不是畏罪潜逃了吧
'cause the asshole is guilty. Couldn't be that,right?
不可能是那样 对吧
'Cause that would mean it would be your fault,right?
因为如果是那样 那就是你的失职 不是吗?
Mr. Dover?
多佛先生.
Mr. Dover? What?
- 多佛先生. - 怎么了?
You need to take care of yourself and your wife.
你得照顾好自己和妻子
That's the best thing you can do right now.
这是目前你能做的最有用的事了
That little girl is gonna need you when she comes home.
等你女儿回来时 她也需要你的照顾
Kids gone for more than a week
我女儿已经失踪一周多了
have half as good a chance of being found,
找到她的机会已经减半了
and after a month,almost none are.
如果超过一个月,那机会就等于零了
Not alive. All right?
即使找到她  她可能也已经死了 对吗？
So forgive me for doing everything I can...
所以 请原谅我不得不竭尽所能...
You know what?It hasn't been a fucking week.
现在连一周都还没到呢 你明白吗?
You're right. It's day fucking six!
你说得对 现在已经是他妈的第六天了!
Day six!
第六天!
And every day she's wondering why
每一天 她肯定都在想
I'm not there to fucking rescue her!
为什么我他妈的还没去救她.
All right. Do you understand that?!
你明白吗？
Me! Not you! Not you! But me!
着急的是我 是我 不是你.
Every day!
每天都是!
So forgive me for not going home to have a good night's rest!
原谅我现在还不能回家好好休息
Now,why don't you look
现在,为什么你他妈的不去找我的女儿·
for my fucking daughter rather than fighting...
而要在这里和我.....
hey,hey,hey,hey,hey,hey.
嘿 嘿 嘿
Don't follow me.
别跟着我.
Mr. Dover. Mr. Dover.
多佛先生 多佛先生…
You don't think I'm gonna let you get behind the wheel
你喝了这么多酒
after you've been drinkin',do you?
你觉得我现在还能让你继续开车吗？
I'm gonna walk.
You look for my daughter.
我走回去 你去找我的女儿吧
Daddy.
爸爸.
Look,daddy,we found it.
爸爸你看 我们找到了.
Anna... Where was it?
安娜 在哪找到的?
I'm not Alex.
我不是亚历克斯
What... what are you saying? What? What?
什么,你说什么? 什么?什么?
I'm... Not... Alex.
我...不是...亚历克斯.
Wait a minute. You're not Alex? What?
等一下 你不是亚历克斯? 什么意思?
I'm not Alex.
我不是亚历克斯.
Just a second. I don't understand.
等一下,我不明白.
Just... just talk to me.
告诉我.
I waited,and he never came.
我一直在等 可他一直没来
Come on. No more riddles.
得了 别再跟我玩谜语了
Just fuckin' tell me.
快他妈的告诉我
I'll let you go home to your aunt
我就让你回家 回去你姑妈那里
if you tell me where they are.
如果你告诉我她们在哪的话
I just wanted to play.
我只是想找他玩而已
Don't make me do this again.
别再逼我做这种事了！
And he never came. Don't make me do it.
- 可是他没有来 - 别逼我！
He never came.
他没有来
I just wanted to...
我只是想....
why are you making me do this?
为什么你一定要逼我这么做？
Help me,God.
主 请帮帮我
Relying on your almighty power
以你全知全能
and infinite mercies and promises,
无尽的仁慈以庇佑
I hope to obtain pardon for my sins.
宽恕我的罪过
Fuck me.
坏了
No... no noise.You shut up.
别出声 你最好乖乖闭嘴
You make any noise,I'm gonna turn on that tap.
你弄出任何动静 我就会打开水龙头
Hey,rise and shine.
嘿 太阳晒屁股了
I'm not gonna find two girls here,am I?
两个小女孩总不会藏在这吧
Fuck you.
去你妈的
What about Alex Jones?
亚历克斯·琼斯怎么样了?
What about him?
他什么样?
I came here to drink.
我过来这喝酒而已.
I don't want to drink in front of my wife.
我不想在我妻子面前喝酒
Look... My father left me this building,all right?
听着 这是我父亲留给我的房子 明白吗?
You mind giving me a tour?
你介意带我参观一下吗?
Why didn't you tell me about this place?
为什么你没有跟我提过这个地方?
I didn't think it mattered.
这和案子没什么关系
Everything matters.
任何事都有关系
It's all pretty much like this.
房子比较破旧
I'm gonna renovate soon.
我正准备重修装修呢.
Yeah.
嗯.
Not as organized as your basement,huh?
没你的地下室整齐
What's up with all the survivor gear in there?
这些生存装备是怎么回事?
Pray for the best,prepare for the worst.
祈求最好的结果 做好最坏的打算
Guess we agree there,yeah?
我也常这么想
Come on,hurry up.
快点 快点
Shit.
该死
Hello?
喂?
The guy that you were looking for was just here.
你要找的那个人刚刚来过了
He saw me watching him and ran.
他发现我在看他 然后他就跑了
You get a plate?
记下他的车牌号了吗?
Yeah.
嗯…
嗯
Yeah.
好
Go home,Mr. Dover.
回家去吧 多佛先生.
Hi.
嗨.
Mornin'.
早上好
Why'd you run away from me the other night,man?
那晚你为什么要逃跑？
I've never seen you before.
我从来没有见过你.
You sure you have the right house?
你没敲错门吧?
You doin' some shopping at the value mall lately?
你最近有去那家商场买东西吗
Yeah.
有啊
Why? Is it a crime to shop there?
为什么这么问？去那里买东西有罪吗？
I can't afford to buy suits from Brooks Brothers.
我又买不起布克兄弟那种档次的衣服
Yeah,I know.
我知道.
You bought children's clothes.
你买的是小孩的衣服
Did I?
有吗?
Must've been in a hurry.
我不记得 可能当时太仓促了
Do... do you have children?
你有孩子吗?
No.
没有.
I don't...Have...
我什么....
Have anything...
.....什么都没有
Come on! Christ!
老实点 该死的!
Give me your fucking hand.
把手给我伸过来
Hey.
嘿.
If you move,I'll put a bullet through your fuckin' head.
如果你敢跑 我就照你脑门来一枪
This is 13-40.
这里是警员13-40.
I need additional unit for search.
我需要一支小队支援搜查...
437 Carrol street.
请派警员前往凯勒街437号
Possible kidnapping victims on the premises.
受害者可能就在屋内
Anna?
安娜
Anna? Joy?
安娜? 乔伊?
Fuck.
操！
Aye! Fuck.
我操！
Ah.
噢
Ah. Fuck.
我操！
Ah.
噢
So we've taken photographs of some of the clothing
我们已经给那些在嫌疑犯的房间里
we found in the suspect's house.
找到的衣服拍了照片
Mr. Dover.
多佛先生
Mr. Dover,is your wife here?
多佛先生,你妻子在这里吗
She's not coming.
她没来.
Well,if you can't make a positive I.D.
好吧,如果你无法准确地辨认
On any of these photographs
这些照片里的东西
I'm gonna need her to come in and take a look at them.
那你的妻子就需要亲自来确认一趟了
Have a seat.
请坐.
So he confessed? He said he killed them?
他是不是已经认罪了？他把她们杀了？
We were hoping he was lying,but...
我们希望他是在撒谎 但...
We haven't even found any bodies,Mr. Dover,but...
我们还没有找到任何尸体 不过...
the birches positively identified
...伯奇先生和太太
two pieces of clothing.
已经指认了两件他们女儿的衣服
I'm gonna need you...
如果你...
I'm gonna need you to tell me if you recognize anything.
如果你能认出什么 请告诉我
No.
不是.
I'm not sure.
我不确定
I don't know.
我不知道.
No.
不是..
That... That's her...
那...那是她的...
That's her sock.
那是她的袜子.
You...
你...
You wasted time.
你把时间浪费了
You wasted time following me.
你浪费时间去跟踪我
You let this happen.
是你害死了她们
Don't talk to them.
不要跟他们讲话
Eliza told me they're dead.
伊莱扎和我说她们已经死了
Is it true?
真的吗?
No.
不.
She said they found their bloody clothes
她说警察找到了沾着她们血的衣服
don't you tell your mother that.
别告诉你妈妈
Don't you dare tell your mother that.
不能告诉你妈妈
You understand me?
听明白了吗?
Now,I need you to listen to me.
现在你听我说
I need you to stay around the house for a couple of days,
这几天你留在家里
and you make sure she does not watch the news,
你要保证不能让她看到新闻
and when the paper comes,
如果有报纸送来,
you just throw itthe fuck away... listen to me!
你就把它们丢掉.听着！
We do not give up on your sister!
我们还不能放弃
We do not!
我们不能!
I'm gonna find her.I'm gonna bring her home.
我会找到她的 我会带她回家
We do not give up.
不能放弃.
You're gonna bring her home? She's dead.
你要带她回家？ 她已经死了
You can't do anything.
你现在什么都做不了.
You've been leavin' me and mom here while you...
你把我和妈妈扔在这里...
you've been goin' out and getting fuckin' drunk!
自己跑到外边去喝个烂醉..
You think I can't smell it on you?!
你以为我闻不到你身上的酒味吗！
Shut up!
闭嘴！
How long has this Bob Taylor been workin' on this map?
这个鲍勃·泰勒折腾这张地图多久了?
Three-and-a-half hours.
三个半小时
And you think this is gonna lead you to the bodies?
你觉得这能让你找到那些尸体?
'Cause I sure as shit don't.
我知道那是不可能的.
Do me a favor,captain.Go fuck yourself.
帮我个忙 巡查长 滚一边去
We weren't getting anywhere questioning him.
问了半天什么都没问出来
That looks more like a maze than a map.
与其说那画像地图 不如说是迷宫
He's got a thing for mazes.
他热衷迷宫一类的东西
I'm goin' home.Call me if somethin' happens.
我先回家了  如果有什么进展 打电话给我
Give me that card,Johnny.The key card.
把门禁卡递给我 约翰尼 卡
All right,it's done now.
好了 你已经画完了
Tell me what you're drawing.
告诉我你画的是什么?
You said you were drawing a map.
你说你要画一张地图,
That looks like a fucking puzzle.
可是这玩意看起来明明是一个迷宫
You tell me what you're drawing.
告诉你我画的是什么东西
Tell me what you're drawing.
I can't!
我不能!
Yes,you can!Yes,you can!Oh,shit!
你当然可以说 你当然能 该死!
Shit!
该死!
Yes,you can!Yes,you can!
你必须说!必须说!
Take him! Come on! Yes,you can!
- 把他拉开,快点 - 必须说！
Yes,he can!
他必须说
Oh,shit!
噢 该死!
Gun! Gun! Gun!
枪!枪!枪！
Bob,don't! Put the gun down!
鲍勃 不要 把枪放下！
Bob. Bob. Put the gun down!
鲍勃 鲍勃 把枪放下！
Bob,Bob,Bob,Bob,Bob,no! No,no,no!
鲍勃 鲍勃 鲍勃 不 不！
No,no,no!
不要!
Fuck.
操
Go call a fuckin' R.A.!
去打电话叫法医来!
Our father who art in heaven,
我们在天上的父
hallowed be thy name.
愿人都尊你的名为圣,
Thy kingdom come,
愿你的国降临,
thy will be done,
愿你的旨意行在地上
on earth as it is in heaven.
如同行在天上。
Give us this day
our daily bread,
赐给我们日用的饮食
and forgive us our trespasses...
赦免我们的罪
As we...
如同 --
As we for...
如同我们--
He explain this before he ate the bullet?
这是他吃枪子之前画的？
I'm sorry.
我很抱歉.
Fuck you're sorry.
抱歉个头
Save it for the girls' parents.
把那些抱歉的话留着跟孩子的父母说去吧.
I don't know what to do,Alex.
我不知道我应该做什么 亚历克斯.
I don't know what to do anymore.
我真的不知道我该怎么办.
And what's completely fucked up about all this
事情会变成这样
is I know you know where they are.
是因为我知道你知道她们在哪
I think we're done.
我想我们已经完事了.
They're in the maze.
她们在图画上这个迷宫里
That's where you'll find them.
那你要去哪里找她们
What?
什么？
What did you say?
你刚说什么?
In the maze.
在迷宫里
What... what... maze?
什么....什么迷宫？
Where is it?Where is the maze?
迷宫在哪里? 迷宫在哪里?
Where do I find it?
怎么才能找到那个迷宫?
Alex?
亚历克斯?
Alex,Alex,listen to me.
亚历克斯,亚历克斯? 听我说.
I'm gonna get you out of here,okay?
我会让你离开这里的 好吗？
Just tell me where the maze is.
只要你告诉我迷宫在哪
That's it.Just tell me,man.
只要你告诉我
Where is the maze?
迷宫在哪
Come on,tell me.
快告诉我
Just tell me where the maze is,okay?
告诉我迷宫在哪,好吗?
Come on,don't fuck with me.
快点 别再玩我了
Don't fuck with me now.
你最好别再惹毛我
Tell me,God damn it!
快说 该死！
Tell me where they are!
告诉我她们在哪!
Tell me! Tell me! Tell me!
告诉我! 告诉我!告诉我!
Something's gonna get to you,man.
你这是自找的
Something's gonna get to you!
你自找的！
Just a minute!
马上就来!
Can I help you?
你有什么事?
Morning,ma'am.
早上好 女士
Um... I'm Keller Dover.
我是凯勒·多佛
Uh,my little girl was abducted with a friend.
我女儿和她的朋友被绑架了
What do you want?
你想干嘛？
Uh...
嗯...
I-I guess I haven't thought this through too good,huh?
我想我...还没考虑好
I...
我...
I've been thinkin' a lot about what happened to your nephew.
我一直在想有关你侄子的事
And I know I scared him
我知道在警察局那天
the other day at the police station,and... and...
我吓着他了,而且...而且...
What I'm tryin' to say is
我想说的是
I kind of feel responsible for him running away.
现在他逃跑了 我觉得我也有责任
You wanna come on in?
你想进来吗？
Yeah.
嗯.
My husband and I were...
我和我丈夫曾经...
Very devout at one time.
非常相爱.
Spent our summers driving around
夏天时我们经常会
in that camper with our son...
开着那辆露营车带我们的儿子四处旅行
Handin' out pamphlets...
给人们发放那些
Spreadin' the good word.
传播上帝福音的小册子.
After our son died of cancer...
自从我们的儿子死于癌症以后
We started seein' things differently.
我们对很多事情的看法都变了
Adopting Alex helped...
虽然收养亚历克斯帮我们走出了阴影
But we never got over it.
但这件事还是很难让人释怀
I'm sorry.
我很遗憾
You look very tired.
你看起来很疲惫
Yeah,I don't sleep much.
这些天我几乎都没睡
I,uh...
我...
I keep dreaming about being lost in a maze.
我总是梦见我在一个迷宫里迷路了
I'm sorry.
我也很遗憾.
Alex never talks very much,so...
亚历克斯不太喜欢说话 所以...
When people come over here,I hardly know what to say.
有人来这里的时候 我也不晓得该说些什么
He doesn't talk much?
他不爱说话?
Well,he talks,you know.
噢 他也不是完全不说话
"Good morning," "good night"...that sort of thing.
不过大都是『晚安』之类
Hard to get too much more than that out of him.
除此之外也没什么了
He had an accident when he was little.
他小时候发生过一次意外.
After that,he started
在那之后 他讲话就变得
choosing his words a little too carefully.
非常小心翼翼
What,uh,what kind of accident did he...
是什么意外导致他...
Oh.
噢.
My husband kept snakes.
我丈夫养蛇...
It wasn't that bad what happened,
其实也不是太糟...
but Alex had a fear of them and...
可是亚历克斯很怕它们...
That's not my favorite memory.
那是一段不太好的回忆.
I'm sorry. It's none...none of my business.
很抱歉 和你谈些有的没的
Oh,it's...
噢,那个...
Can I get you a cup of tea,Mr. Dover?
我帮你倒杯茶吧 多佛先生?
Oh.
噢
Oh,I'm so sorry.
噢 对不起
I thought you had known about that already.
我以为你已经知道了
I say it's better this way.
我觉得对于那个恶毒的男人来说
You know,that awful man,
这样的结局再好不过
he would have spent years on death row
否则他的余生恐怕也得在死囚牢房里度过
just watchin' TV and gettin' fat.
每天只能看看电视 越来越胖
Well,least I don't have to worry about losing you to PSP.
起码我不用再担心你会被局里处分了
When forensics is finished with the guy's place,
等法医清理和鉴定完那个家伙的房子后
we're gonna deploy the cadaver dogs.
我们就得派出警犬去搜寻孩子们的尸体
Look,kid,we can't always save the day.
听着 孩子 我们不可能总是胜利
All right? We're just cops,janitors.
对吗? 我们只不过是警察而已
So you lost this one,all right?
这次我们已经失败了 明白吗
Look,you want fulfillment,you need to find a girl,
听我说 如果你想要有成就感 那就去找个女孩
you know,start a family,have some kids.
结婚成家 生些孩子
Let it go.
让件事过去吧
Yeah?
喂?
Hey,it's Rich.We found somethin'.
我是瑞奇 我们有新发现
Guys,let us have a look.
伙计们 让我们看看
Two kid-sized department store mannequins,
两个百货商店的假人
with their heads caved in.
被砸烂了脑袋
I just talked to our lab guys,
我刚跟实验室的人通过电话
and they told me that all the blood that we sampled
他们说我们之前提取的
from the plastic containers pig's blood.
那些塑料容器里的血样都是猪血
All right,you guys,let's get this covered up.
好吧 伙计们 把这些都盖上吧
It's supposed to snow soon.Hurry up,okay?
这里很快就要下雪了 动作快点
It's like he's play-acting.
他似乎是在玩角色扮演
I mean,case in point.
我的意思是
Except for the few items I.D.'d by the Dovers and the Birches,
除了多佛先生和布奇先生家孩子们的衣服之外
all the kids' clothes that we found
我们找到的其他衣服上
still had the tags on them.
都还挂着商店的标签
And that maze book that we found,he made it.
还有 那本迷宫书
Photocopies,pictures from this book
是他自己做的影印本
that we found in the attic.
原本是在阁楼上被发现的
Ex-F.B.I. Agent wrote that.
作者是一位前联邦调查局探员
"Finding the Invisible Man."
《发现隐形人》
Yeah,it's about a theoretical suspect that he believed
是关于一个
was responsible for a bunch of child abductions.
儿童绑架案的嫌疑人的
It's totally discredited,I guess,
我觉得可信度不高
but I read some of it.
不过我读了一部分
Taylor... Taylor was abducted when he was a kid.
泰勒 泰勒小时候也被绑架过
He ran away after three weeks.
不过三周后他逃出来了
And the captor drugged him
绑架他的人喂他吃了
on some sort of LSD/Ketamine cocktail.
氯胺酮和迷幻剂混合出来的麻醉药
He never remembered. They never caught the guy.
所以他什么都不记得了 警察最终也没抓到那个罪犯
Okay,so...
所以说...
He read the book
他是读了这本书
and decided he was taken by the invisible man.
决定假扮被这个隐形人抓走的孩子
Now he's doing his best imitation,right?
现在他又开始模仿这个隐形人 是么？
Yeah,he was doing his best imitation.
对 他在尽力模仿这个隐形人
He killed himself last night.
昨晚他自杀了
How did he do that? I thought he was in custody.
怎么会这样 我以为他还在拘留所呢
Hey.
嘿.
Taylor drew this.
泰勒画了这个
It's a map to the bodies.
这是一张藏尸地的地图.
And we found the same design on a pendant
我们前几天在那个地下室里的尸体上
that we pulled off that corpse the other day.
也找到了与之相同的图案的挂坠
There's a connection. Okay?
这肯定有某种关联 明白么?
The connection is that it's the last maze in the book.
所谓的关联就是 这是这本书里的最后一个迷宫图
I did it. It's unsolvable.There's no way out.
我试解了一下 是个没有出口的迷宫
Your corpse is another wannabe who read the book.
那具尸体可能是这本书的另外一个模仿者
What are you saying to me,Rich?
你什么意思 瑞奇?
What are you saying to me? What are you saying?
你想说什么? 你想表达什么?
That... that...that this guy is a fake?
你想说这人只是个假货?
You're saying that the girls...
你想说那些女孩....
the girls are still out there somewhere?
那些女孩仍然还在其它什么地方？
How did Bob Taylor get those clothes?
那鲍勃·泰勒是怎么拿到那些衣服的？
How did... how did the parents...
为什么...她们的父母
Positively I.D.Those clothes?!
能指认出那些衣服?
That I can't reconcile.
这个 我也解释不了
You can't reconcile that?
你解释不了?
Just keep knockin' on doors,look in the windows.
就去继续敲门调查就好
Hey,why is that there? Bag that.
为什么那玩意还在哪里? 快装起来..
Will do,sir. Right away.
好的长官 马上
Yes?
你好?
Um,yeah. This is she.
对 是我
What?
什么?
Oh,my God!
噢 上帝呀
Uh,wait. Is she...?
噢,等等,她是不是...?
Ralph! Keller!
拉尔夫 凯勒!
Keller! We need to go to the hospital!
凯勒! 我们得去医院
They found joy,but not Anna! What?
她们找到乔伊了,但是没找到安娜. 什么?
They didn't find Anna!
她们没有找到安娜!
Maybe she'll know where Anna is! Please,we have to go!
也许她会知道安娜在哪 ! 我们现在过去！
Keller!
凯勒!
Eliza's not picking up.
伊莱扎不接电话
You should text her.
你应该发短信给她.
Yeah.
我发了.
Nobody gets beyond this point.
你们不能过去
Don't touch me.
别碰我!
Miss! Wait a minute...
女士 请等一下!--
It's okay.
没事的.
Nancy.
南茜.
Grace.
格蕾丝
They'll find Anna. I know they will.
- 他们会找到安娜的,- 会的.
I know they will.
我知道他们会的
I know.How is she?
我知道. 她怎么样了?
Is she awake?
她醒着吗?
Joy,were you far from our street?
乔伊 你之前在什么地方？
How far from the street were you,Joy?
离这里远吗,乔伊?
Joy?
乔伊?
You can't be doing this now.
你现在不能问她问题
How long did it take you to get there?
那里离我们街区多远?
Just let me ask a question! Please. Keller!
- 就让我问这一个问题就好 求你了 - 凯勒!
The detective will be back in just a minute.
警探马上就会回来这里
You need to wait.
你就等一会吧
She's been drugged.
她被麻醉了
Joy.
乔伊
Sweetheart...
宝贝...
Just let us know she's alive,okay?
告诉我们她是不是还活着 好吗?
Can you just nod your head,baby?
宝贝 你可以点一下头吗?
Just nod your head? Baby?
就点一下头 好吗宝贝?
Can you give us a nod?
你可以点一下头吗?
Can you nod your head for us,please? Joy?
可以点一下头吗?求你了,乔伊.
Joy?
乔伊?
You were there.
你当时也在那里...
What? I was... I was where?
什么？我在哪里？
It put tape on our mouths.
他们用胶带把她的嘴封上了
Shhh.
嘘
It's okay.It's okay,baby.
没事 宝贝 没事的
It's okay. It's okay.
没事的,没事的
Mommy and daddy are here now,okay?
爸爸妈妈都在这里
You're all right.
你还好吗？
Excuse me. You're all right now.
抱歉 你现在没事了.
I said nobody's allowed in that room but her family.
我说过除了她的家人谁都不能进病房
Hey! Where you goin'?
嘿 你要去哪里??
Keller?
凯勒?
Hey! Where's he goin'?
嘿 他要去哪里?
I don't know. Hey!
- 我不知道. - 嘿!
Call downstairs. Don't let him go.
叫楼下的人注意 别让他跑了
Hey! Hey! Block off the exits.
站住！ 堵住出口.
Hey!
嘿!
Stop that car! Get his truck!
截住那辆车 截住他!
Stop it! Hey! Hey!
别跑,嘿! 嘿!
I've got you,you fucker.
你跑不掉的 混蛋
I know where you're goin'.
我知道你要去哪 .
我知道你要去哪
Hello again.
你好.
Hey. I was hoping you'd,uh,you'd let me do some penance.
我希望你...能让我做点什么 弥补我的过错
For what?
为什么?
For scaring you the other day at the,uh,the police station.
之前在警察局的时候我吓到你了
You already apologized for that.
你已经道过歉了
I know. I was... you know,I thought maybe you,uh...
我知道 我只是觉得...也许...
You could use some,uh,help around the...
也许我可以帮你做点什么...
you know,I noticed your door here needs fixing,
我注意到你的门需要修理
so I brought my tools and,uh...
所以我带来了工具 而且...
Oh.
噢.
I see.
我明白了
I burned myself.Feel a little icky today.
我把自己烫伤了. 今天感觉不太好
But I'm glad you want to talk some more.
我很高兴你还想要谈谈这事
No need to make excuses.
不过也用不着找什么借口
You come on in and make me a cup of tea.
你进来吧 顺便帮我泡杯茶.
Come on in.
请进.
I don't want to have to hurt you.
我不想伤害你.
I know they were here.
我知道她们在这里.
Put your hands on your head and turn around.
把手举起来 转过身来
Do it.
照我说的做.
I'm just gonna go.
我这就走.
Don't touch that bag.
别碰那个包
Put your hands on your head.
把手放到头上
Come over here to this counter.
走到台子这来
Come on!
快点!
Top drawer.
最上边的抽屉
Open it.
打开它
Put them on.
自己戴上
You don't know me,Mr. Dover.
你不了解我 多佛先生
But believe me when I tell you,I won't let you go.
但是相信我 我不会放你走的
You don't have to drink all of it.
不用全喝完
About a third should do for a man your size.
像你这样的体格 三分之一差不多
Something to make you more manageable.
那会让你变得老实一点
Forget it.
想都别想
Drink it,Mr. Dover,
喝掉它 多佛先生.
or I'll kill you right here in my kitchen
要不我只好在厨房动手了
and bring your daughter in here
然后我会把你女儿带来这里,
and have her scrub your brains off the floor...
让她来把地板上的你的脑浆擦干净
Where is she?
她在哪?
Drink.
快喝.
Just let me see her.
让我见见她.
You want to see her? Yes!
- 你想要见她? - 对
That's your ticket to your daughter right there.
把那个喝了 我就带你去见女儿
A little more,Mr. Dover.
再多喝一点 多佛先生.
Little more.
再多一点.
Good,isn't it?
味道不错,不是吗?
That's my darlin' husband's recipe.
那可是我亲爱的丈夫的秘方.
Now go on out back.
现在我们到后院去
Let me see her.
让我见她.
Take it out of your pocket.
把手机从你的口袋里拿出来
Put it in the sink.
扔进水槽里
Put it in the disposal.
扔到污水处理槽里.
Put your car keys on the table.
把你的车钥匙放在桌子上.
That's right.
这就对了.
Over to the trans am over there.
那边 那辆通用汽车
The car over there.
那边那辆
Come on,move it. Get over there.
快走 到那边去
The look on your face.
你脸上的表情.
My husband used to have the very same look...
和我丈夫当时的表情太相像了...
Till we took Alex.
直到我们抓走了亚历克斯.
He was the first kid we ever took.
他是我们抓走的第一个孩子.
His name was Jimmy.
他的本名叫吉米.
Or Barry.
或者巴瑞?.
Can't remember. Doubt he can,either.
我不记得了 我怀疑连他自己也不记得
So many names.
名字太多了.
Forgot all about Bobby Taylor
我几乎都已经忘记鲍勃·泰勒了
till I read about him in the paper.
直到我在报纸上发现了他的新闻
Get in the driver's seat.
坐到驾驶座上
Open the door and get in the car.
打开车门 进去车里.
Making children disappear is the war we wage with God.
让孩子们一个个消失 就是我们向上帝宣战的手段
Makes people lose their faith.
让人失去他们的信仰
Turns them into demons like you.
让他们变成像你一样的恶魔
Had to slow down since my husband disappeared.
自从我丈夫失踪以后 我不得不放慢速度
But I do what I can.
但是我依然在尽我所能
Start the car.
点火
Keep tryin'.
继续
Back up. Slowly.
倒车 慢点.
Come on. Back up.
倒车.
Come on.
快点
Stop.
停车
Turn it off.
熄火
Turn it off!
熄火!
Get out.
下来
Think you should know.
我想告诉你一件事
Alex never laid a hand on those girls.
亚历克斯从来没有碰过那些女孩
Just wanted to take 'em for a ride in the camper.
他只是想要带她们去兜风而已
I was the one who decided they should stay.
是我决定要把她们关在房子里的
Take a look.
看那里
Maybe your daughter's under there.
也许你女儿就在下面
You never know.
谁知道呢.
Anna.
安娜!
Anna!
Anna?
安娜!
Anna. Anna!
安娜!安娜!!
Anna!
安娜!
Anna?!
I had the girls down there
警察过来的时候
when the police came pokin' around.
我就让那些女孩待在下面
Should have left 'em down there.
我该让她们一直待在那儿的.
I was so lonely without Alex.
但亚历克斯不在的时候 我觉得非常孤独
Now get in there.
现在进去那里.
What?
什么?
Get in.
进去.
You want me to get in there,you're gonna have to shoot me.
除非你给我来上一枪 不然我不会进去的
I'm not gonna get in there just 'cause you asked.
凭什么你让我进去我就进去
Go on. Get in there.
快点 进去
That's right. That's right.
很好 这就对了
Make yourself a tourniquet.
给你自己弄个止血带吧
Just might last 24 hours.
你大概还能撑个24小时
I'd love for you to still be alive
我希望你能活到
when I dump your daughter's body down there.
我把你女儿的尸体扔进去的时候
Wait! No,wait,wait,wait!
等等!不 等等 等等！
Wait!
等等！
No.
不.
不！
Hey.
嘿
I need you to go over to Holly Jones.
你去通知下赫莉·琼斯
She needs to be notified.
关于他侄子的事
No. I need to find Dover.
我需要你帮我找到多佛
Come on. You're done with Dover,okay? Please?
你不要再操心多佛了 求你了行么
You want me to go to Holly Jones?
你想让我去找赫莉·琼斯？
I want you to go to holly Jones' and notify her,please.
我想让你去通知一下赫莉·琼斯
Oh,God.
噢 上帝啊.
Almighty God...
全知全能的主...
Protect my girl.
求您保护我的女儿
Mrs. Jones?
琼斯女士?
琼斯女士？
Show me your hands right now.
马上举起手来
Don't move and show me your fuckin' hands right now.
别动 马上把你的手给我举起来
Stop! Right now!
别动!听见没有！
Show me your fuckin' hands.
把手举起来
Do not move and show me your hands.
别动 举起手来
Make sure they cremate me.
记得让他们火化我
I sure as hell don't want to be buried in some box.
我可不想躺在什么木头箱子里
Both hands! Right now!
两只手 快点！
Right now!
快点！
Fuck!
操!
Anna.
安娜.
Oh,my God.
噢,天哪.
Oh,God.
Anna.
安娜.
Oh,shit.
该死.
Come on. Come on. Anna. Anna. Come on.
安娜 安娜 坚持住 坚持住
Stay with me,Anna.Anna,stay with me,huh?
别睡着 安娜 不要睡着
Stay with me,Anna!
坚持住 安娜!
Stay with me,Anna! It's all right!
坚持住 安娜! 已经没事了!
It's all right! Come on!
没事了! 坚持住!
Go,move,move,move,move!
快点 快点 快点
Don't die,don't die.
不要死 不要死
It's okay,it's okay.
到了 到了
Honey. You're okay.
宝贝 你不会有事的
Hey.
嘿.
Hey! Help!
嘿！来人帮忙！
Help! Help!
医生！医生！
Help!
医生!
Uh,detective Loki?
洛奇警探?
I hope we're not intruding.
希望我们没有打扰到你.
No.
没事
She's doing real good.
她恢复得很不错.
She's gonna be up and around in a few days,
过几天就可以走路了
aren't you,buddy?
是不是 宝贝？
She just wanted to come and say thank you and hi to her hero.
她想要过来跟她的英雄打个招呼 还有谢谢你
Hello.
你好.
Uh,would you mind giving me a minute?
介意我单独和他谈谈么
Yeah. Thank you.
- 行 - 谢谢
Say Goodbye,joy. Bye.
- 乔伊 说再见 - 再见
I'll be out in a minute.All right?
我很快出来 好吗?
Say goodbye,Anna.
说再见 安娜.
She found her whistle?
她找到她的口哨了?
Uh,no.
噢 不是这样的
She keeps insisting that Joy helped her find it
她一直坚持说  口哨是感恩节那天
on Thanksgiving before they were taken.
她们被带走前 乔伊帮她找到的
But I think she's just confused.
可是我觉得她的脑袋还有点糊涂.
I got her a new one.
是我给她买了只新的
He hasn't contacted me.
他还没有跟我联系过.
I know you don't...
我知道你不会...
I know you probably don't believe that,but he hasn't.
我知道你可能不相信我 但他真的没有联络过我.
I-I believe you.
我相信你
Do you think you're gonna find him?
你觉得你能找到他吗？
Yeah.
嗯
And he'll go to jail.
他会进监狱么
Probably.
也许.
Anyway...
总之...
Thank you for everything.
谢谢你所做的一切.
Oh,God.
噢 天哪.
I miss him.
我真的很想他
He... He did what he had to do to find Anna,
他那么做只是为了找到安娜
and I thank God for that.
感谢上帝能保佑他.
He's a good man.
他是个好人
Bye.
拜拜.
That's it.Let's pack it up.
就这样吧 收工了
You all done for the night?
今晚的活都干完了?
Yeah,the ground's frozen solid.
对 地面都已经冻住了
It's gonna take weeks to excavate the entire property.
要把这片地方都挖开 起码得一个礼拜
Just found some dead snakes and shit.
目前为止我们只找到了一些死蛇什么的
Pray for the best,prepare for the worst,yeah?
祈求最好的结果 做好最坏的打算 对吗?
Night.
晚安.
Shut her down.
把机器关了吧